toursbylocals.com 2017-04-17

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

ToursByLocals is committed to maintaining your privacy. ToursByLocals.com gathers certain types of information about you as part of our operations. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how you may correct or change that information.

Information Collected by ToursByLocals.com  
ToursByLocals.com collects two types of information about you - personal information (such as name and e-mail address) and aggregate information (such as information about how many users visit our site).

Personal Information  
Personal information is collected when you voluntarily purchase services or register as a user. This may include e-mail address, passwords, telephone numbers, address and other data needed to provide services to you.

We will only require the minimum personal information we need and use it only to provide the services you have requested.

Full Names Displayed in Reviews  
By default, your first and last name is displayed with any guide reviews you post. If you would like to only have your first name and the first letter of your last name displayed, uncheck the 'Display full name' option in the 'Account Options' section after you log in.

Messages Sent Through the System  
ToursByLocals provides a method for communicating with the guides on our system. We may monitor these messages for the purpose of ensuring that you are properly served by our guides and to ensure compliance with the terms and conditions of ToursByLocals.

Aggregate Information  
We may collect aggregate information about overall user activities online such as the number of unique visitors, pages accessed most frequently or the search terms entered. This information may tracked through your Internet Protocol (IP) address, a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. When you request a page from our site, your IP address may be logged. We may also collect aggregate information through the use of a cookie, which is a small data file that Web sites store on your hard drive when you visit them. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies however you can adjust your browser settings to refuse or alert you when cookies are being sent. However, some parts of our sites, may not function properly if you choose not to accept cookies.

We use aggregate information to improve your user experience by determining which areas and features are most popular and which may need to be improved. ToursByLocals does not use IP addresses or cookies to retrieve any information from your computer.

Sharing Data with Third Parties  
ToursByLocals does not distribute personal information that you have shared with us, except as permitted in this Privacy Policy and our then-current Terms of Use, if any.

ToursByLocals can share your personal information in case that we are required to by a lawful request such as a subpoena or if we believe that the health or safety of another person or the general public may be compromised.

ToursByLocals uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information, but some of the information may be processed by servers or other information systems that are located in the United States of America or elsewhere, and disclosure of information stored on or transmitted through those servers or services could be compelled under the USA PATRIOT Act; although it is highly unlikely for something like that to happen, it’s important for you to know.

Some of the Personal Information we collect is shared with our tour guides who are directly involved in fulfilling the purchases you have made from us. We only provide our tour guides with your name and your local contact details if you provide them (e.g., your hotel name for pick-ups and drop-offs, your local phone number, your mobile phone number, etc.) We do not provide our tour guides with your email address or any other Personal Information.

We use third party vendors for email delivery and web analytics purposes, in order to improve your user experience and deliver you the most relevant content from ToursByLocals. These vendors never share or sell your personal information.

Links to Third Parties  
This site may contain links to sites other than our own and those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as ToursByLocals.com. If you visit other sites by clicking on a link from our site, you should determine their privacy policies before using their information or services.

Opting Out  
You can choose to remove your e-mail address from our database at any time. To do so, please send an e-mail to info@ToursByLocals.com.

Correcting and Updating Information  
ToursByLocals.com provides you with the ability to change and modify information previously provided. Please follow the appropriate link when you log into your account.

Additional Information  
No one can guarantee that transmission of data over the Internet is completely secure. It may be possible for third parties to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communication. While we strive to protect your personal information, ToursByLocals.com cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and we shall not be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages you may suffer in the event that your transmission of data was intercepted.

ToursByLocals.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted online.

Please contact us via e-mail at info@ToursByLocals.com if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy.

Last Updated: February 2, 2017
